（詩音(しおん)）
圭(けい)ちゃん…圭ちゃんってば！
Kei-chan.
Kei-chan, are you listening?
聞いてますか？
（圭一(けいいち)）あっ…
Y-Yeah, I'm listening.
（圭一(けいいち)）うん聞いてるけど
（詩音）あの…
Um, is it true that gramps
Kimiyoshi is missing?
公由(きみよし)のおじいちゃんが
行方不明になったって本当ですか？
えっ公由？
Kimiyoshi?
Oh, the village headman?
ああ村長さんのことか
うんどうやらそうらしいけど
Yeah, so I heard.
（詩音）はいどうしよう…
私昨日村長さんに―
What should I do?
Yesterday, I told the village
headman about that night.
あの晩のこと打ち明けたんです
（圭一）えっ？
It's my fault!
（詩音）私のせいです
よせよ詩音のせいじゃないよ
Stop it. It's not your fault.
No, it is!
いいえ私のせいなんです！
だって打ち明けてすぐなんですよ
Because he disappeared
right after I told him.
その晩すぐに消えてしまって…
He suddenly
disappeared that night.
話したから殺されてしまったんだ
打ち明けたから殺されてしまった…
He was killed because I told him!
He was killed
because I confessed!
They kill those
who are close to me...
親しい人たちから
順に殺していって
さんざん
悲しい思いをさせたあとに殺す
...have me suffer a lot,
and then kill me.
That's their plan!
そういうねらいに違いないんです！
That's awesome.
すげえよそれ…
すごいアイデア！すごい残酷！
What a great idea. How brutal.
R-Rika-chan!
I also told Rika-chan!
（圭一）り…梨花(りか)ちゃん…
俺も梨花ちゃんに話したんだ
- "Eye Opening" Chapter -
Episode 06: CONDEMNATION
When They Cry
Behind where I looked back
(who's there in the front)?
I raised my nails in the dark
(and slashed the night).
Raindrops become droplets of
blood and drip down the throat.
If you don't have
a place to go back to...
...then stop here on my finger.
I'll take you away
along with that finger.
To the unopenable
forest where cicadas cry.
You can't turn back anymore.
（ﾚﾅ）
梨花ちゃん沙都子(さとこ)ちゃんいる？
Rika-chan! Satoko-chan!
Are you there?
梨花ちゃん沙都子ちゃん！
Rika-chan! Satoko-chan!
It's locked.
鍵がかかってる
２階の窓とかは？
窓が開いてるかもしれない
What about the second-floor
windows? They might be open.
圭ちゃんハシゴ
Kei-chan, ladder.
I'll check the main house.
私本家のほう見てくるね
（圭一）本家？
Main house?
（詩音）古手(ふるで)家の本家だよ
The Furude main house.
梨花ちゃんの両親が亡くなって以来
ずっと放置してあるそうだけど
I heard it's been left alone
since Rika-chan's parents died.
Oh, right.
Rika's parents...
あっそうか
梨花ちゃんの両親って…
Satoko's too.
（詩音）沙都子もだよ
Her parents fell off a cliff due
to Oyashiro-sama's curse...
オヤシロさまのたたりってことで
両親が崖から落っこちて
お兄さんの悟史(さとし)君も
いなくなっちゃって…
...and her brother
Satoshi went missing.
それ以来梨花ちゃんと沙都子は
ここで一緒に暮らしてるんだよ
Since then, they've been
living here together.
That's right.
そうだ沙都子と梨花は親友同士
Satoko and Rika are best friends.
The reason why only
Satoko hasn't been cursed...
沙都子だけが
たたりに遭わない理由…
それは古手梨花の力が
あったせいじゃないの？
Is it because of
Rika Furude's power?
It must be hard on them.
（圭一）２人とも大変だな
（詩音）ハッ…
She's cursed.
呪われてるんだよ
（圭一）えっ？
“呪われてる”って言ったの
（圭一）なっ…
I said she's cursed.
（ハシゴの揺れる音）
み…魅音(みおん)？
M-Mion?
Satoko Hojo received
Oyashiro-sama's curse entirely.
北条(ほうじょう)沙都子はね
オヤシロさまのたたりを
一身に受けた呪われた子なの
When the entire Hojo
family is destined to die...
死の運命に
のみ込まれた北条家の一員なのに
沙都子だけが
許してもらえるなんて！
...how could Satoko be
the only one forgiven?
悟史君を差し置いて！
Leaving Satoshi-kun behind?
許せない許せない
許せない許せない！
Unforgivable! Unforgivable!
お…おい落ち着けよ魅音！
H-Hey, calm down, Mion.
Unforgivable!
Unforgivable! Unforgivable!
許せない！許せない！許せない！
Mi-chan! Keiichi-kun!
（ﾚﾅ）魅ぃちゃん圭一君
鍵借りてきたよ
I borrowed the key!
落ち着け…古手梨花はもう死んだ
Calm down.
Rika Furude is already dead.
オヤシロさまの生まれ変わりは
死んだんだ
Oyashiro-sama's
reincarnation is dead.
アア…
（詩音）オッ…助かったね！
Good save.
ねっ？圭ちゃんエヘッ…
Right, Kei-chan?
この雛見沢(ひなみざわ)には
今やたたりをなす神はいない
In Hinamizawa, there is
no one who can curse others.
それを決める資格は…
I have the capability
to decide that.
私にある
（村人Ａ）見つからんか？
Have you found them?
No, but we haven't looked there.
（村人Ｂ）いや…
でもあっちのほうはまだだ
Let's go.
（村人Ａ）魅音ちゃん！
（詩音）あっ…
Mion-chan!
（村人Ａ）沼のほうも
ぐるっと捜したけど全然ダメだね
We looked around the marsh,
but we couldn't find anything.
（村人Ｂ）
明るくなんないと分かんないよね
We can't tell till
the sun comes out.
（詩音）
うんありがとうございます
Thank you.
婦人部の皆さんが集会所のほうで
豚汁作ってくれてますんで―
The women are making pork
stew in the assembly room...
休んでください
...so please get some rest.
（村人Ｂ）そういえば
梨花ちゃんがいなくなったってのは
By the way, who was the first to
realize Rika-chan went missing?
誰が最初に気づいたんだ？
（詩音）あっ…
Oh, Kei-chan...
He said he had a weird feeling.
（詩音）あ～圭ちゃんだけど
虫が知らせたんだとか
That's a little...
そりゃちょっとな…
（村人Ｃ）なんや怪しいんと違うか
Isn't that a little suspicious?
ハッ…私の発言ひとつで
圭ちゃんを悪者扱いだよ　面白(おもしれ)え！
Just from my one statement,
Kei-chan is now accused.
How fun!
Well, well, this smells good.
（大石(おおいし)）おやおやおや…
（詩音）あっ…
（大石）
このいい匂い…豚汁ですかな？
Could it be pork stew?
I would definitely
want some of that.
こりゃ是非
ご相伴にあずかりたいものですねえ
（詩音）大石め私がホシだと
当たりをつけてやがるか
That Oishi already thinks I'm
suspicious and is investigating.
フッ…かまうものか
Who cares.
You murderer!
（沙都子）人殺し！
Did gramps Kimiyoshi die?
（詩音）
公由のおじいちゃん死んだ？
ああなるほど
Oh, I see. So you saw him die.
見たんだ？ 断末魔　ウフフフッ…
（沙都子）
よくもみんなを！梨花を！
How dare you do this
to everyone... To Rika...
私をどうするつもりなんですの？
What are you going to do to me?
I'll kill you.
（詩音）殺す
（沙都子）ハッ…
Stop! Don't kill Satoko!
（魅音）
やめて！沙都子を殺さないで！
アハハハッ！今ごろ命請いかい？
You're pleading for her life now?
You didn't do that for Satoshi-kun.
あんたは
それを悟史君のときに しなかった
（詩音）それがあんたの罪なんだ
（魅音）ハッ…
That is your sin.
Forgive her!
許してあげて！
私はどうなってもいいから
沙都子を許してあげて！
I don't care what happens
to me, so forgive Satoko!
I was screaming
like you that time.
（詩音）
今叫んでるお前はあのときの私
どんなに叫んだって
届かない救えない助けられない
No matter how you scream...
...it won't reach her.
You can't rescue or save her!
お前は
そこで苦しみを味わうがいい！
You shall experience pain there!
Stop!
やめて！やめてやめてやめて！
Stop! Stop! Stop!
よ～し…じゃこうしよう
Okay, then let's try this.
Say, "I'm sorry," 1,000 times.
1,000回
“ごめんなさい”って言うんだよ
そしたら沙都子を解放してあげる
Then I'll let Satoko go.
I'm sorry!
ごめんなさい
ごめんなさいごめんなさい…
ごめんなさい ごめんなさい…
（沙都子）アアッ！
ハハハハッ！
泣くのはあんたの専売特許だね
You have a patent
on crying, don't you?
泣けばにーにーが
助けに来てくれるのかな？
Will your nii-nii come
and save you if you cry?
Satoko, can you hear my voice?
（詩音）
沙都子私の声が聞こえる？
（殴る音）
（詩音）聞けよこら！
Listen, you!
Do you understand your sin?
あんたは
自分の罪が分かってるの？
どれほど悟史君を追い詰めていたか
知ってる？
How much you ran
Satoshi-kun down?
Nii-nii... Nii-nii...
Yes, all you had
to do was cry for nii-nii.
（詩音）そうあんたは
“にーにー”って泣けばよかった
泣きさえすれば
いつも悟史君がかばってくれた
As long as you cried,
Satoshi-kun protected you.
でもね悟史君の
負担ってものを考えたことある？
But have you thought about
the burden you placed on him?
悟史君は
あんたのヒーローでもなければ―
Satoshi-kun isn't your hero,
nor is he immortal.
不死身でもない
Just like you!
（詩音）あんたと同じに…
（沙都子）ハッ…
What's wrong?
どうしたのよ？
もう右腕の感覚がない？
Have you lost feeling
in your right arm?
じゃ左腕にするか！
Then let's switch to the left hand.
どうしたの？
叫ぶと私を喜ばすから―
What's the matter?
Crying out makes me happy,
so you resist screaming?
せめて悲鳴を上げずに
抵抗ってわけ？
Yes. I thought so too.
（沙都子）
ええ私もそう思っていましたのよ
（沙都子）私が
にーにーを追い詰めたから―
That Nii-nii disappeared
because I ran him down.
いなくなってしまった
（詩音）ハッ…
I was spoiled.
私が甘えていた
にーにーもつらかったはずなのに
Even though he
was also suffering...
...I couldn't stop myself
from clinging on to him.
私はにーにーに
すがりつくことをやめられなかった
（詩音）
ちょっと意外自覚があったとはね
That was a little unexpected.
So you were aware?
（沙都子）にーにーは
きっと帰ってきてくれるんですの
Nii-nii will definitely come back.
When he does, I'll show
him how much I've matured.
帰ってきたら私―
一人前になってるところを
見せるんですのよ
私もうにーにーの背中に
隠れたりしないって―
I'll show him that I don't need
to hide behind his back anymore.
見せてあげるんですの
（詩音）アハハハッ…
帰ってきたらいいねえ
Wouldn't that be nice
if he came back?
Nii-nii will definitely come back!
にーにーは
絶対に帰ってきてくれますの！
（沙都子）
それまで待ってるんですのよ
I'll wait till he does.
I'll apologize to him for
relying on him so much.
今まで甘えてきて本当に
ごめんなさいって謝るんですの
I won't give up till then.
それまで負けるものか！
No matter how painful
it is, I won't rely on him.
どんなにつらくても
にーにーに甘えたりしない
泣いたら今までと一緒だから―
Nothing will change
if I cry, so I'll endure it.
私は耐えて…
耐えてみせるんですのよ！
I'll show you I will!
Don't think
you're tough, you brat.
上等抜かすな小娘が！
私を刺して楽しいなら
いくらでもお楽しみあそばせ！
If stabbing me entertains you,
then stab till you're satisfied!
でもね私は泣かないんだから！
But I won't cry.
絶対絶対！絶対！
（詩音）ヤッ！ヤッ！
Never! Never! Never!
（刺す音）
にーにー見てますわね？
Nii-nii, are you watching?
Satoko has become
this much stronger.
沙都子は
こんなに強くなったんですのよ
もう何が起きても
へこたれませんの
No matter what, I won't give up.
こんな程度で…
（刺す音）
Not to something like this.
こんなくらいでは私は泣かない
（詩音）ヤーッ！
Something like this
can't make me cry.
あっ悟史君！私も待ってたんだよ
Satoshi-kun,
I've been waiting for you.
最後に
言葉を交わしたときからずっと
Since the last time
we exchanged words.
（悟史）
魅音沙都子のこと頼むからね
Mion, I'm leaving
Satoko to you, okay?
I had forgotten
Satoshi-kun's last and only wish.
私…悟史君の最後の
たったひとつの願いさえ忘れてた
こんな私を悟史君は
絶対迎えになんか来ない！
Satoshi-kun will never come
back to a person like me.
私を…こんな私を…
A person like me... Like me...
ああなんだ…私
自分でも知ってたんじゃないか
Oh, yeah.
I knew it too.
こんな私は
もうとっくに鬼だったんだって
That I had become a demon.
When They Cry
（詩音）圭ちゃんが全ては私
園崎(そのざき)魅音の犯行だと悟って―
Kei-chan found out that
I committed all the crimes...
...and came to the Sonozaki
main house the next day.
園崎本家にやって来たのは
次の日のことだった
ハハハハッ！これは
とんだ名探偵が身近にいたもんだよ
There was
a supersleuth nearby, huh?
（詩音）
まさか冷蔵庫の中身だけで―
Figuring it out just from a call and
what was in the refrigerator...
電話の内容まで見破るとは！
Mion, the police are
already suspicious of you.
（圭一）魅音警察はもうとっくに
お前を疑っているんだ
Oishi's crew is waiting for their
chance to break into this house.
この家も
大石さんの部下が踏み込もうと―
今も様子をうかがっている
弁解はしないよ
私には鬼が宿ってる
I won't make excuses.
A demon dwells within me.
自首しよう　私たちも一緒に行くよ
Turn yourself in.
We'll go with you.
We'd never leave
our best friend alone.
親友を
１人きりになんか絶対にしない
最後のわがまま聞いてほしいな
Can you listen
to my last selfish wish?
その前に30分でいいから
圭ちゃんと２人きりにしてほしい
Before that...
...I'd like you to leave me and
Kei-chan alone for 30 minutes.
腕…組んでもいいかな？
May I hold your arm?
あっ…別にかまわないぞ
I don't mind.
It seems Shion also liked you.
（詩音）詩音も
圭ちゃんのことが好きだったみたい
Really?
（圭一）そうなんだ？
（詩音）もう私は―
I couldn't tell whether
I was Shion or Mion anymore.
自分が詩音なのか魅音なのか
分からなくなっていた
Only the word "demon"
appeared in my mind.
ただ“鬼”の１字
そればかりが頭に浮かんだ
Come with me.
I want you to see all of my crimes.
来て
私の罪の全てを見てほしいから
But they might be
horrific sights for you.
でも それは圭ちゃんにとって―
この上もなく
つらい光景かもしれない
Nothing will change.
I'll keep saying it.
変わらない　何度だって言う
園崎魅音は俺の最高の親友だ
（詩音）あっ…
Mion Sonozaki is my best friend.
Idiot.
バカ…カッコよくなんかないぞ
That didn't look cool at all.
I'm a demon, so I don't get
what people feel anymore...
私は鬼だから―
もう人間の気持ちは
よく分からないけど
...but I think I understand
a little of why she liked you.
あの子が
あんたを好きになったのは―
ちょっと分かる気がする
Kei-chan?
（魅音）圭ちゃん？
あっ…詩音！
Shion!
詩音か？あっ…
Is that you, Shion?
圭ちゃん…圭ちゃん！圭ちゃん！
Kei-chan? Kei-chan! Kei-chan...
良かった無事だったんだな
Thank goodness you're okay.
（魅音）
イヤー！もうイヤ！イヤー！
No!
I can't take this anymore! No!
落ち着け詩音もう終わったんだ
Calm down, Shion. It's over.
ようやくお目覚め？
You're finally awake?
I'll kill her after she hears...
あの子に自分のせいで
死ぬ大勢の人の悲鳴を―
...the screams of all the people
who'll die because of her.
たっぷり聞かせてから殺すの
Isn't it a great plan?
なかなかいいセンスでしょう？
ウフフフッ…
Who are you?
お前は誰だ？
はぁ？園崎魅音でしょう
Mion Sonozaki.
You can't possibly be Mion.
お前が魅音であるはずがない
私が本当は詩音だって
見破ったの？
Did he figure out
I'm really Shion?
鬼だ…この鬼め！
You're a demon.
A demon!
返せ！魅音を返せよ！
Give her back! Give back Mion!
Give me back
my best friend, Mion!
俺の
最高の友人だった魅音を返せ－！
Don't give up, Mion!
Don't lose to this demon!
（圭一）頑張れ魅音！
こんな鬼に負けるな！
Show me your true strength!
ホントに強いお前の力を
見せてくれ！
（詩音）フフフフッ…圭ちゃん
私を笑い涙で溺れ殺すつもり？
Kei-chan, do you plan to drown
me in tears of laughter?
Please, Mion! When did
you lose to this demon?
アハハハッ！
（圭一）頼むよ魅音！
どこで お前は
こんな鬼に負けちまったんだ？
お前は
こんな弱いヤツじゃないだろう！
You're not this weak!
負けるな戦え！
Don't lose! Fight!
（詩音）圭ちゃんどうしても
知りたがっているようだから―
Kei-chan, since it seems like
you desperately want to know...
...I'll tell you one thing.
ひとつだけ教えてあげるよ
The demon dwelled
in me for quite a while.
私の中に鬼が宿ったのは随分前
だけど私は
それを理性で押さえつけた
But I suppressed
it with reasoning.
鬼はそれで収まり
The demon settled down with that,
and I thought it went away.
私は どこかへ
行ってしまったんだろうと―
思い込んでいた
But I was wrong.
（詩音）でも違った
The demon was
just sleeping inside me.
鬼は私の中で
眠っていただけだったの
The demon was awakened
by one small thing.
その鬼はある小さなことを
きっかけに目覚めてしまった
You're the main reason
why everything got screwed up.
あんたが全てを狂わせた
元凶なんだよ 圭ちゃん
（魅音）人形をくれなかったんだよ
He didn't give me the doll.
（詩音）魅音が泣いて
私に心の内を打ち明けた
Mion cried and
confessed her feelings.
As I heard her speak, I started
to remember Satoshi-kun.
（詩音）
それを聞いているうちに―
私は悟史君のことを思い出した
（圭一）アアッ…
あのときあんたがもらった人形を
魅音に渡していたなら
If you had given
that doll to Mion...
...then everything might
not have screwed up.
全ては
狂いださなかったかもしれない
No way.
そんな…
When I tortured everyone else,
I didn't hesitate a bit, but...
（詩音）
ほかの人を拷問するときは―
何のためらいも
なかったんだけどね
If that'll calm Mion's demon,
do it until you're satisfied.
（圭一）
それで魅音の気が済むのなら―
好きなようにやってくれ
Really?
本気？
Compared to Mion's pain,
this isn't anything, right?
（圭一）俺が傷つけた魅音の
痛みに比べれば―
こんなの大したことないんだろう
In exchange,
promise me two things.
その代わり２つ約束しろ
詩音は許してやれ
Forgive Shion.
The other is to please
give that body back to Mion.
もうひとつは
その体を魅音に返してやってくれ
それだけだ
That's it.
You're not even thinking
about begging for your life?
命請いするとか
そういう考えは思い浮かばないの？
じゃ３つ目は“俺を殺すな”だ
Then the third one
is not to kill me.
最初に２つって言ったんでしょう
だからもうダメ
You said two initially.
So no more.
That's too bad.
そいつは残念
多分私は約束を守らないよ
鬼だから
I probably won't keep
the promises since I'm a demon.
But I don't mind granting
just your third wish.
でも今の３つ目の願いだけは
聞いてあげてもいいよ
To give this body back to Mion...
That's impossible now.
“この体を魅音に返すこと”
それももうムリ
It's not! Mion is Mion!
そんなことはない魅音は魅音だ！
もう戻ってこないなんて言うな！
Don't say she can't come back!
Can you hear that sound?
Since you weren't coming back,
Rena probably called Oishi.
（詩音）帰りが遅いから
レナが大石を呼んだってとこかな
（詩音）ごめんね魅音を汚(けが)して
I'm sorry for desecrating Mion.
ここに入る前に約束した
Before I came, I promised.
何があっても
俺の中の魅音は変わらない
No matter what happens,
the Mion within me won't change.
でも忘れて　今日以後
私を見かけても近寄らないでね
But forget about it.
Even if you see me after today,
don't come near me.
It'll just be the demon
that possessed my corpse.
これは私の屍(しかばね)に取りついた…
鬼なんだから
（圭一）ウッ…
アア…
（詩音）さあ出ておいで
Come out.
Kei-chan's just old cold
due to the stun gun.
圭ちゃんは
スタンガンで伸びてるだけ
もうすぐ警察隊が来るから
解放されるよ
The police will come soon,
so you'll get rescued.
あ…ありがとう
（泣き声）
Thanks.
But you still have things to do.
I'm going to escape from here.
でもあんたにはまだ用がある
ここから脱出するの
Hurry!
早く！
（魅音）あっうん…
Go down there
and apologize to Satoshi-kun.
底まで落ちて悟史君に謝っといて
（魅音）詩音！
Shion!
（魅音）この底にはね
悟史君はいないんだよ
Satoshi-kun isn't down there!
（詩音）
はぁ？あんた言わなかったっけ？
Didn't you say so?
That he was dumped there?
“この底に捨てられてる”って
I also liked Satoshi-kun!
So I confronted Granny.
私もね
悟史君のことが好きだったんだよ
だから
ばっちゃに詰め寄ったんだよ
絞め殺してやろうかってくらい！
そしたら…
I even thought about
choking her to death. Then...
（魅音）
園崎家は手を下してないって
...she said the Sonozaki
family had nothing to do with it.
（詩音）ウソだ！
- Liar!
- I don't think she was lying.
私はばっちゃが
ウソをついているとは思わない
She even allowed your
relationship with Satoshi-kun!
だって 悟史君と詩音の交際
ばっちゃは許したんだよ
ハッ…
（魅音）爪を剥いでみせたから―
You tore your nails, so she said
she'd forgive and forget it all.
全てを許して忘れるって
（詩音）ウソだウソだ！
Liar! Liar!
Then who erased Satoshi-kun?
（詩音）じゃ誰が
悟史君を消したっていうのよ？
I don't know.
（魅音）それは分からない
But doesn't the curse
happen because someone...
（詩音）だってたたりは
園崎家がほのめかしたことを―
...carries out the Sonozaki
family's suggestions?
誰かが実行するから
起こってるんでしょうが！
Granny researched
that for a long time...
それも
ばっちゃが長いこと調べたんだって
でもね誰もやってないの
...but no one did it.
There's no one in the village
who does such things!
そんなことしてる人
村の中には誰もいないんだって！
No way. Then that means those
I've killed weren't for revenge?
ウソ…だってそれなら―
私が殺したのは
敵(かたき)じゃないってことに…
アハハハッ！やるね
You're good.
So you're trying
to reverse my revenge plan?
最後に私の復讐劇(ふくしゅうげき)を
ひっくり返そうってわけ？
Shion, believe me.
I'm not a target of revenge.
詩音信じて
私は敵なんかじゃない信じてよ
Believe me!
もしあんたが無実なら―
If you're innocent...
...then you can go to heaven
and see Satoshi-kun!
あんたは天国に行って
悟史君に会えるね！
The suspect fled the scene.
（大石）容疑者は現場より
逃走したもよう　繰り返します…
Repeat. The suspect
seems to have fled the scene.
容疑者は現場より逃走したもよう
Keiichi-kun! Keiichi-kun!
圭一君！圭一君！
（魅音）死ね！
（詩音）ハッ…
Die!
早く死ね！
お前は呪われてるんだよ
Hurry up and die! You're cursed.
あれだけのことをして
生き延びるつもりか？
You plan to live
after doing all that?
ウワーッ！
お前なんか死んでしまえ！
（ドアをたたく音）
You should just die!
死ね！死ね！死ね！
Die! Die! Die! Die!
死ね！
（詩音）うるさ～い！
Shut up!
ハハハハッ！ざまあみろ！
In your face!
（詩音）フフフッ…
お久しぶり　元気してた？
Long time no see.
Were you doing well?
（圭一）お前こんな所を
うろついてて大丈夫なのかよ？
Is it okay to be
wandering around here?
どうしたんだよ？こんな時間に
What's the matter at this hour?
私ねもうここにはいられない…
I can't stay here anymore.
おい大丈夫か？
Hey, are you okay?
I've tried hard u-until today...
今日までが…頑張ってきたけど
...but I can't anymore.
もうダメ…
ハハッ…アハハハッ…
（圭一）おい…
Hey.
アハハハッ…
（圭一）大丈夫かよ？
Are you okay? Don't overdo...
ムリするな…
アハハハッ！間に合った
I did it in time! I did it! Did it all!
できた！ 全部できた！
褒めてよ悟史君！
Congratulate me, Satoshi-kun!
Hurray! It's all over.
（詩音）やった！これで終わった
悟史君ごめんね約束守れなくて
Satoshi-kun, I'm sorry
I couldn't keep the promise.
I'm sorry, everyone.
ごめんねみんな…ごめん
I'm sorry.
This time, I won't make
the mistake. For sure.
今度は間違えないよきっと…
To get my happiness,
I had done everything...
...but had done nothing
to be blamed and accused of.
The sound of footsteps
became louder every day.
Then I noticed the fact
there was no time.
I was a believer in life,
to be myself always.
And was asking
whether I would be alive.
Give me a reason
why not to adopt in this way.
Or judge me to be guilty
of so many incurable sins.
Tell me why or why not?
Complaining way too much.
Maybe I overlooked
something fatal for me.
Preview
What catches you
is the afterimage of the past.
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）
とらわれるのは過去からの残像
What invites you is the false
image from the future.
いざなうのは未来からの虚像
What is there is another joke.
そこにあるのはもうひとつの戯れ
When They Cry.
「ひぐらしのなく頃に」
"Atonement" Chapter,
Episode 1: HAPPINESS.
- "Atonement" Chapter -
Episode 01: HAPPINESS
"Atonement" Chapter,
Episode 1: HAPPINESS.
- "Atonement" Chapter -
Episode 01: HAPPINESS
Can you believe it?
あなたは信じられますか？